You're going to use Android Studio to create the
detail activity from the blank activity with fragment template.
The template asks for the hierarchical parent of detail
activity, which defines the up button noted by the
app icon, and a left pointing carrot here. But
what does up mean? If you mapped out a
hierarchy of all screens in the sunshine app, the
root of the tree would be the main activity, and
it's child would be the detail activity. So, the
app goes to the main activity. While the back button
can achieve the same effect, it can also bring
you back home or to another app, depending on your
history of screens. Up will always navigate you within
the same app to the parent, regardless of how you
arrived at this screen. Create the detail activity now,
and look at how the activity is declared in the
Android manifest file.